Guys today I just came to tell you I've
chicos hoy me vengo de decir me he
smoked three joints Selin and Chokes yes or
fumado tres porros selin y chocas sí o
no What do you think What's up my kids I
no Qué pensáis Qué pasa mi chavalería
'm Javi Oliveira welcome one more day
Soy Javi oliveira bienvenidos un día más
to my channel I hope you are Enjoying the
a mi canal Espero que estéis Disfrutando
dam the shipping between Shokas and Seling
del dam el shipeo entre shokas Y seling
both LoL streamers is
ambos streamers del LoL se está
intensifying more and more in fact it
intensificando cada vez más de hecho se
is starting to get confused if it really is
está empezando a confundir si realmente
a ship or if it is something
se trata de un ship o se trata de algo
real in this video we are going to try to
real en este vídeo vamos a intentar
reach a conclusion and I want you to
llegar a una conclusión y quiero que me
help me Although it is true that
ayudéis Aunque si es verdad que el
Chokes on his tiktok has already confirmed
chocas en su tiktok ya ha confirmado
this The relationship of the
esto Se confirma la relación de los
streamers Joaquín Domínguez better known
streamers Joaquín Domínguez más conocido
on the internet as Chokes known
en internet como el chocas conocido
streamer writer bodybuilder
streamer escritor culturista director de
film director astronomer mathematician shooter physicist
cine astrónomo matemático tirador físico
and cook and Alicia González alias eelin
y cocinero y Alicia González alias eelin
after many rumors of their alleged
después de muchos rumores de su supuesta
relationship this afternoon in a
relación esta tarde en una transmisión
live broadcast they decided to break the
en directo han decidido romper el
silence with this gesture guys it's
silencio con este gesto chicos es
official
oficial
people are still trying to explain to each
la gente se sigue intentando explicar
other how that guy has
entre ellos un servidor como ese tío ha
managed to have a girlfriend but I love her
conseguido tener novia pero la quiero
so much that it doesn't matter anyway
tanto que da igual en fin 33 añitos
the creature is 33 years old  very important if you
tiene la criatura es muy importante si
want to comment on this video I pressed
queréis comentar en este vídeo que pulsé
the subscribe button okay If you didn't
el botón de suscribiros vale Si no os
subscribe if you don't click it You're going to try to
suscribí si no le dais Vais a intentar
comment on the video but your
comentar en el vídeo pero vuestro
comment is going to go way down So
comentario se va a ir muy para abajo Así
press the subscribe button which is
que pulsar el botón de suscribir que
completely free and you're going to
completamente gratuito y te vas a
find out about everything I upload is serious
enterar de todoo lo que subo es en serio
that chocas your partner like this we've been
que chocas tu pareja así llevamos cu
together for four not five years Celin which is that you
años juntos cuatro no cinco celin que es
have a memory in case someone hasn't
que tienes una memoria por si alguien no
caught it I have to say Of course
lo ha pillado tengo que dejar Claro que
these clips are a joke or not and the thing is that
estos clip son de broma o no y es que
everything you're seeing so
todo lo que estáis viendo hasta el
far all the clicks that I just
momento todos los clicks que acabo de
put are on the chocas tiktok account
poner están en la cuenta de tiktok del
exclusive 100% confirmed I
chocas exclusiva 100% confirmado Le
just asked Celin I just or
acabo de preguntar a celin Le acabo o
rather this guy personally I just
sea este chaval personalmente Le acabo
asked Cel if she is Chocas's girlfriend
de preguntar a cel si es la novia de
And this is his answer Hey by
chocas Y esta es su respuesta Oye por
the way, cpe hadn't been given a
cierto a cpe no le habían regalado un
cushion with my [ __ ] face on it why isn't he
cojín con mi [__] cara por qué no lo
wearing it he's wearing it in his ass
tiene puesto lo tiene puesto en el culo
Oh I understand someone in the chat wants to
Ah entiendo algui en el chat quiere
activate the train  hipe thanks Good
activar el tren del hipe gracias Buen
day know for giving a nikin Thank you very much
día sepan por regalar un nikin Muchas
er la nu del chocas
gracias er la nu del chocas
Yes but who has given him who has
Sí pero quién le ha dado quién le ha
given him permission to make our thing public
dado permiso para hacer público lo
this does not mean that there has to be
nuestro esto no supone que hay que tener
a consensus before that point
un consenso antes de que ese punto
arrives and the fact is that at the moment there is no
llegue y es que en estos momentos no hay
topic that is being talked about more
un tema del que se esté hablando más
on Twitch Spain specifically which is
sobre Twitch España concreto que es de
the possible relationship between shokas and selin
la posible relación entre shokas y selin
Well in fact what has been
Bueno de hecho de lo que se está
talked about the most in recent days is
hablando más en los últimos días es de
the relationship between shokas and selin and the
la relación entre shokas y selin y del
physical change of ibai which by the way
cambio físico de ibai que por cierto
what a change even in face the
Vaya cambio incluso de careto el cambio
physical change of ibai is incredible I mean you
físico de ibai es increíble o sea
just have to see The before and
solamente hay que ver El antes y el
after In such a short time you just have to
después En tan poco tiempo solamente hay
see The before and after In such a
que ver El antes y el después En tan
short time I think this man is
poco tiempo yo creo que este hombre está
taking cocaine because if not I cannot
tomando cocaína porque es que si no no
explain it if not the cuoca the buts
me lo explico si no la cuoca el peros
tell me when are we going to see each other
dime cuando nos vamos a ver
and there are many people who do not even fit
y hay mucha gente incluso que no encaja
his new face because it is that by losing
su nueva cara porque es que al perder
so much weight in such a short time the skin
tanto peso en tan poco tiempo la piel
has not yet assimilated it the face has
todavía no lo ha asimilado la cara ha
shrunk and it looks very strange it does not seem ibay
encogido y se ve muy raro no parece ibay
From  in fact there are people who are not
De hecho hay gente que está tampoco
used to seeing Oh come on and he is not
acostumbrado a ver Ah va y que no está
completely obese they are claiming
completamente obeso que están afirmando
that he was better off before than now something
que estaba mejor antes que ahora algo
that is not even close to crazy,
que ni de
look like a [ __ ]
coña parce gonor [__]
like he says [ __ ] Why did his head
como dice [__] Por qué la cabeza se le
get so small dude, look like that
puso tan chiquita huevón parce ese
[ __ ] How is he going to lose weight dude
[__] Cómo va a adelgazar cráneo parce
This is very weird bro I do not believe
Esto está muy raro bro yo no me creo
this photo bro I mean it is okay to lose weight
esta foto bro o sea está bien adelgazar
dude but does his head look like a [ __ ] why did his head
huevón pero hace [__] la cabeza por
get so long and so so
qué se le puso así tan larga y tan tan
long dude no what I can not
lonina huevón no lo que yo no puedo
understand is the
entender es la
head I mean his skull what the
cabeza o sea su su cráneo qué huevón
[ __ ] How the [ __ ] can you reduce
Cómo [__] puedes reducir huesos
cranial bones is what I do not I do not see
craneales es lo que yo no yo no le veo
any explanation Well that is what is
explicación alguna Pues a eso que está
weird Yes you understand me I can tell you
raro Sí me entiendes te lo puedo decir
bro it is weird maybe many of those
bro está raro tal vez a muchos de los
who are coming to the video do not sound
que estáis llegando al vídeo no suene De
shocka or selling is welcome since
nada el shocka o selling ya que a
unlike other influencers that we
diferencia de otros de los influencers
are talking about lately
de los que estamos hablando últimamente
on the channel, these two in particular as
en el canal estos dos en concreto como
such are not youtubers but are more
tal no son youtubers sino que están más
present in other social networks Like
presentes en otras redes sociales Como
for example Twitch which is where
por ejemplo Twitch que es donde
these two are mainly although
principalmente están estos dos aunque
also especially in the case of shas he
también sobre todo en el caso del shas
usually has a lot of viral clips on
suele tener muchísimos clips virales en
tiktok and on Twitter too, I mean, you
tiktok y en Twitter también o sea yo que
already know that on Twitter I
ya sabéis que en Twitter me dedico a
comment on news about streamers and
comentar noticias de los streamers y
viral things and so on,
cosas virales y demás siempre se
the clips that I upload of shocka always go viral a lot
viralizan mucho los clips que subo del
and it is usually quite
shocka Y es que suele ser bastante
controversial shocka is one of the
polémico el shocka es uno de los
most followed video game streamers in
streamers de videojuegos más seguidos en
Spain on Twitch and you have probably
España en Twitch Y probablemente te
come across a tiktok or some
hayas encontrado con un tiktok o algún
viral clip since as I was
clip viral ya que como os estaba
saying, it is usually quite
diciendo suele ser bastante
controversial there are children dying of
polémico hay niños muriéndose de
c and what the last time that I remember
c y qué la última vez que yo recuerde
having commented on a controversy
haber comentado una polémica
starring choca as such I mean yes, it may have
protagonizada por el choca como tal O
appeared in other
sea sí que ha podido aparecer en otros
videos but adored by him if I remember
vídeos pero avado por él si no recuerdo
correctly tell me the comment box but I
mal decidme la caja de comentarios pero
think it was because of the issue of
creo que fue por el tema de las
multi-accounts choca He had a controversy in
multicuentas choca Tuvo una polémica en
which they caught him using multi-accounts
la que le pillaron usando multicuentas
where he sucks his dick He also
donde se autochupa el [__] Así mismo se
praised himself and also From that
auto alababa y además también Desde esa
multi-account he insulted some
multicuenta insultaba a algunos
colleagues with whom he actually
compañeros con los que en realidad se
gets along well, for example he threw auron at him he
lleva bien por ejemplo le tiraba auron
threw  I was like eh if you don't have the
le tiraba ibai eh si no tenéis la
personality to have an account
personalidad como para tener una cuenta
m with which to say all your [ __ ]
m con la que decir toda vuestra [__]
stay quiet okay stay quiet
quedaros callados vale quedaros callados
If you don't have the balls to say
Si no tienes los [__] de decir las
things to someone's face don't say them behind their
cosas a la cara no las digas tampoco a
backs either [ __ ] eh if I have something
las espalda putita eh yo si tengo algo
to say I'll tell you from the
que decir te lo digo desde la cuenta
Main account the most popular account the one they
Main la cuenta más popular la que le
caught on screen and the one that was
pillaron en pantalla y de la que más se
talked about the most was called Caty vipi that's why
habló se llamaba Caty vipi por eso
when we catch
cuando le pillamos multicuentas a
someone with multiple accounts we call them the Caty vipis of
alguien le decimos las Caty vipis de
these people but he also had an
estas personas pero también tenía una
account called Eugenio that was
cuenta que se llamaba Eugenio que la
dedicated exclusively to messing
tenía dedicada exclusivamente a meterse
with me or rather like I have a
conmigo o sea como yo tengo aquí un
gossip channel here and I criticized a lot of things
canal de salseo y criticaba muchas cosas
about him well there was a time when
de él pues hubo una época época en la
we had a certain rivalry today
que tuvimos cierto pique a día de hoy
for my part at least it doesn't exist I don't
por mi parte por lo menos no existe no
know for his not at the moment if one
sé por la suya no de momento si algún
day I get silly you shut up
día me pongo tontorrón te callas la boca
But he had an account on both YouTube
Pero tenía una cuenta tanto en YouTube
and Twitter called Eugenio Eugenio
como en Twitter llamada Eugenio Eugenio
lul dedicated to me don't tell me this
lul dedicada a mí no me digáis que esta
account Eugenio is the one who crashes always
cuenta Eugenio es el chocas siempre
appears when I criticize  You crash 300
aparece cuando critico al chocas 300
viewers on Twitch and 1900 on YouTube You
viewers en Twitch y 1900 en YouTube Tú
weren't the father of choca Haha channels
no eras el padre de choca Jaja canales
recommended I 85 chocas 12000 gref
recomendado I 85 chocas 12000 gref
20,000 and you Here scratching from them with
20.000 y tú Aquí rascando de ellos con
3000 Haha that they don't steal content
3000 Ja eso que ellos no roban contenido
like you Javi since he sucks his dick so much
como tú el Javi ya que tanto le chupa la
has 3000 members even knows how many
pija tiene 3000 miembros sabe hasta los
members I have what lastim has 52
miembros que tengo qué lastim tiene 52
followers and the first follower he has
seguidores y el primer seguidor que
is the official Podemos account
tiene es la cuenta oficial de podemos
Pablo Iglesias is behind this
está Pablo iglesia detrás de esto
Selin family on the other hand is a
familia selin por su parte es un
League of Legends streamer or better
streamer de League of Legends o más
known as LoL known for
conocido como LoL conocida por
participating in the streamer event of
participar en el evento de streamers de
the evening of the year where it was canceled
la velada del año donde fue cancelada
for some words against the
por unas palabras en contra de los
Mexican fandom Look, Argentines are
fandom mexicanos Mira los argentinos son
good people, Peruvians are good people,
buena gente los peruanos son buena gente
Chileans are good people,
los chilenos son buena gente los
Mexicans no, I can't stand you, I'm going to beat you
mexicanos no no soporto os voy manar a
all, you're [ __ ] annoying Crazy,
todos me tenéis hasta los [__] Loco
how [ __ ] annoying you are And how [ __ ] annoying
qué [__] pesados sois Y qué [__] pesados
And what disgusting comments and how disgusting  of
Y qué asco de comentarios y qué asco de
fandom And how disgusting it all is, crazy What a [ __ ]
fandom Y qué asco de todo loco Qué [__]
bore you all are really, [ __ ] what a [ __ ]
[__] dais de verdad [__] qué [__]
bore I'm going to venerate everyone who
[__] voy a venar todos todo el que
has the wood to venerate a [ __ ] pran
tenga la maderita a vener un [__] pran
the photo of rivers there rivers queens you give
la foto de rivers ahí rivers reinas dais
[ __ ] cringe She is also known for a
[__] cringe también es conocida por una
toxic relationship she had for a
tóxica relación que mantuvo durante un
while with another LoL player
tiempo con otro jugador del LoL que se
named Antonio. This relationship ended
llama de Antonio esta relación terminó
badly since the boy being her ex
fatal ya que el chico siendo su ex
continued to be her simp, which made
continuaba siendo su simp cosa que hizo
her end up exploding because the
que ella terminase explotando porque el
guy wanted to contact her
tío quería contactar con ella
constantly trying to get back with
constantemente intentando volver con
her Although the truth is that other
ella Aunque la verdad es que otros
creators Like for example the million who
creadores Como por ejemplo el millor que
know them both, did not see the controversy
los conoce a ambos no veía la polémica
in the same way and did not see it well that
de la misma forma y no vieron bien que
Selin explodes and exposes herself like that to Antonio's
selin explotas y exponerse así a Antonio
entry on Twitch But that's why better
la entrada de Twitch Pero por eso mejor
than anyone can say it no like you
que nadie lo puede decir no en plan no
shouldn't do that I'm going to freak out
se debería hacer eso voy a flipar en
seriously And if I screw this up I have to
serio Y si esto lo [__] lo tengo que
say it chat gives it a funny touch
decir chat le da un toque toque gracioso
that he doesn't have a voice Telling me things to
de que no tenga voz Diciéndome cosas
return dude I mean nightmare no it doesn't
devolver tío O sea que pesadilla no no
exceed dude it's that it doesn't exceed everything the
supera tío es que no lo supera todo los
balls already crazy There  too many things that
[__] ya loco Hay demasiadas cosas que
are wrong with this clip Hey, it leaves me
están mal en este clip Eh me deja
alone dude, pissing on you for viid bro
tranquila loco lo mearte de por viid bro
because it leaves me alone it's very heavy
porque me deja tranquila es muy pesado
okay sincerely it seems like an
vale sinceramente me parece una
atrocity to me on Celina's part there is another
atrocidad por parte de Celina hay otro
clip there are more clips I'm telling you seriously I
clip hay más clips os lo digo en serio
find this somewhat atrocious like for
me parece esto algo atroz en plan por
now I'm going to give my opinion on this that
ahora voy a dar mi opinión de esto que
a person sends you a message saying they
una persona te envía un mensaje diciendo
want to get back together it's not harassment it's not
que quiere volver no es acoso no es nada
bad at all When you have had an
malo Cuando has tenido una relación
intimate relationship with someone you can have the
íntima con alguien puedes tener la
freedom to send you messages or say
libertad de mandarte mensajes o de decir
anything in private And if for
cualquier cosa en intimidad Y si tú por
some reason you don't want to know about those
alguna razón no quieres saber de esos
messages or you need space or want to
mensajes o necesitas espacio o quieres
cut that relationship short it's very
cortar por los sano esa relación es muy
easy you block it's very easy you have the
fácil bloqueas es muy fácil tienes la
option to block you have the option
opción de bloquear tienes la opción de
not to communicate with the other person and you
no comunicarte con la otra persona y tú
can't what you can't do is that your
no lo que no puedes hacer es que tu
ex-partner sends you a message to get back together
expareja te envía un mensaje de volver
as if they have sent it to you 50 times if you
como si te lo ha enviado 50 veces si tú
have received 50 messages because you have
has recibido 50 mensajes porque tú has
wanted to receive 50 messages but well I'm
querido recibir 50 mensajes pero bueno
not going to waste time in this video
no me voy a entretener en este vídeo a
commenting on the controversies that
comentaros las polémicas que han tenido
each of the two have had Because both Selin
cada uno de los dos Porque tanto selin
and Shoka are two creators who  they've
como shoka son dos creadores que
each had a few what I would like to
cada uno lo que sí que me gustaría
highlight because it may have to do with
destacar porque puede tener que ver con
the shipping we have today is
el shipeo que tenemos a día de hoy es
How her relationship with Antonio began,
Cómo comenzó su relación con Antonio
notice how this user here sums it up. She
fijaros cómo lo resume este usuario de
earned her career because of Antonio, she
aquí se ganó su carrera por de Antonio
left him and when he tried to get her back she
lo dejó y cuando él intentó recuperarla
called him a stalker when Antonio
lo funo por acosador cuando Antonio
started playing MC with another girl, I don't
empezó a jugar con otra chica al MC no
know if in
sé si en
Minecraft, she started stalking him and sending him
Minecraft empezó a acosarlo y a mandarle
jealousy messages And it's from what I've
mensajes de celo Y es que por lo que he
been looking at before making this
estadoa mirando antes de hacer este
video and this will probably give us a lot
vídeo y esto probablemente nos dé mucho
to talk about for another video later on,
que hablar para otro vídeo más adelante
Selin also started her relationship with
selin también comenzó su relación con
Antonio in a somewhat similar way to what we
Antonio un poco de manera parecida a lo
're seeing today with the
que estamos viendo a día de hoy con el
shas jokes, many interactions that
shas bromas muchas interacciones que se
in the end turned into a relationship in which
convirtieron al final en una relación en
she benefited
la que ella salió beneficiada
professionally, she doesn't love you Antonio
laboralmente ella no te quiere Antonio
LoL is Spanish, on top of that, he's Spanish, he
LoL es español encima es que encima es
speaks to me in English and and he only
español me habla en inglés y y solo me
speaks to me but what does that man say yes I do
habla pero qu dice ese si yo sí te
love you, I mean he's going sideways, that
quiero o sea va de lado ese
man Yes, that click that you just saw It
hombre Sí ese click que acabáis de ver
was from before she was a couple and
Era de antes de que fuese en pareja y
another controversy surrounding Selin that I do
otra polémica en torno a selin que sí
want to mention is one  controversy that
que quiero mencionar es una polémica que
had this same year a few
tuvo este mismo año hace unos cuantos
months ago Because someone was
meses Porque alguien la la estaba
harassing her with multiple accounts there was someone
acosando con multicuentas había alguien
who was creating many
que se estaba creando muchas
multiple accounts on social networks
multicuentas en redes sociales de manera
anonymously hiding without knowing who it is
anónima escondiéndose sin saber quién es
to harass her according to her zelin How good
para acosarla según ella zelin Que bueno
After 2 and a half years of harassment from an
Después de 2 años y medio de acoso de un
absolutely deplorable fan who knew
fan absolutamente deplorable que sabía
everything she did who had
todo lo que hacía ella que tenía
various accounts to continue being a pain in the
diversas cuentas para seguir dando por
ass in the end after a
culo al final después de una
police investigation she will be able to
investigación policial va a poder
report him and she will be able to devirtualize
denunciarlo y va a poder desvirtualizar
it because he really was a guy who
lo porque de verdad que era un tío que
was an obsession the investigation has
era una obsesión la investigación ha
lasted 10 months or so 10 months of
durado 10 meses o sea 10 meses de
putting up with a [ __ ] crazy person
aguantar a un [__] loco
commenting on them for comparing But it would be
comentándoles por comparar Pero sería
ironic to say the least that selin who has been
irónico cuanto menos que selin que ha
stalked by a person with
estado perseguida por una persona con
multiple accounts ends up with shokas and with Katy
multicuentas acabe con shokas y con Katy
vipi in bed oh oh normally the
vipi en la cama oh oh normalmente los
ships are usually created by the
shipeos suelen ser creados por los
fandom and then maybe fueled
fandom y después si acaso alimentados
by the creators themselves to give it a
por los propios creadores para darle un
little life and benefit
poco de vidilla y beneficiarse
financially from it for example one
económicamente de ello por ejemplo uno
of the most recent cases that  it
de los casos más recientes que se me
happens to me is the case of wesc that well
ocurre es el caso de wesc que bueno a
westcol normally his fandom tends to
westcol normalmente su fandom suele
chip him enough with a lot of
chipear lo bastante con un montón de
girls with all the ones that approach him
chicas con todas las que se le acercan
in the last months despite having a
en los últimos meses a pesar de tener
girlfriend They have even been chipping him with
novia Incluso le han estado chipe con
six or seven different streamers which
seis o siete streamers diferentes las
have increased in number
cuales han subido de número
considerably after this
considerablemente después de esta
nonsense And wcol is not that
tontería Y eso que a wcol no es que le
fond of this type of content
haga mucha gracia este tipo de contenido
but equally his fandom continues to chip him
pero Igualmente su fan siguen chipeo
every time a woman approaches him
cada vez que se acerca una mujer a él
with that woman because just in case By the way
con esa mujer porque por si Por cierto
today we will see him in The
hoy lo veremos en Los juegos del
Squid Games wc surely by the time he is
calamara wc seguramente para cuando esté
uploading You can see this video on
subiendo Este vídeo lo podéis ver en
Kick doing multistream on Twitch since he
Kick haciendo multistream en Twitch ya
has even canceled his trip to the
que incluso ha cancelado su viaje a los
gramis to participate in this event
gramis para participar en este evento
So most likely during this
Así que muy probablemente durante esta
week wc will be one of the participants
semana wc sea uno de los participantes
with the most viewers in the series and
con más espectadores de la serie y
also the perfect target for
también el blanco perfecto para los
ships I can't believe it dude
shipeos yo no puedo creerlo huevón a lo
up to this point Uy dude dude with
bien hasta este punto Uy socio parce con
orrea dude and my parents are 27
orrea huevón y es que mis papis tengo 27
years old and have three children I'm going to tell you
años y tres hijos yo les voy a decir
something dude This chipping has been long
algo huevón Este chipeo ha sido largo
what a son of a [ __ ] warriors daddy those
qué hijo de [__] más guerreros papi esos
[ __ ] those [ __ ] haven't deserted
[__] esos [__] no han desertado
those [ __ ] haven't deserted dude
esos [__] no han desertado huevón
because I've had several and daddy they don't
porque yo he tirado varios y papi no
desert they don't desert dude if it goes
desertan no desertan huevón se es más
further he was recently roleplaying in a
lejos hace poco estuvo roleando en una
Minecraft series pretending to be
serie de Minecraft haciéndose las de
Julieta's boyfriend in the game girl of kx
novio en el juego de Julieta girl of kx
who is a girl who went on to have 50,000
que es una chica que pasó a tener 50.000
viewers doing this shipping in the
espectadores haciendo este shipeo en el
role with wc following her lead and this
rol con wc siguiéndole el rollo y esta
girl was heavily criticized because
chica fue muy criticada porque al
apparently she was acting like a hyper mega feminist and
parecer iba de hiper mega feminista y
such And of course suddenly out of interest she
tal Y claro De repente por interés se
kept her feminism to herself and started
guardó su feminismo y se puso a
collaborating with wol the rush that
colaborar con wol el subidón que pegó
Julieta got with the challenge is nameless
Julieta con el desafío no tiene nombre
but it was in the last few days it was all
pero fue en los últimos días fue toda
wescol root no What is wescol do I have to
raíz de wescol no Qué es wescol tengo
suck his dick to get a
que chuparle la pija yo para subir un
little bit wescol I love you
poquito wescol Te quiero
wc what makes the chipeo of
wc lo que hace diferente al chipeo del
shocka with selim different is that this time it
shocka con selim es que en esta ocasión
is a chipeo both created and
es un chipeo tanto creado como
fueled by the creators themselves in
alimentado por los propios creadores de
fact to the followers of both I would say
hecho a los seguidores de ambos Yo diría
that  the shipping does not matter at all
que les da completamente igual el shipeo
and in fact they make fun of the
y de hecho se burlan todo el tiempo del
shipping between the two of them all the time to the point that it is already
shipeo entre ambos al punto de que ya es
a meme on both channels and there are some
un meme de ambos canales y hay algunas
quite viral Twitter and tiktok accounts
cuentas de Twitter y tiktok bastante
that have helped spread the
virales que han ayudado a extender el
rumor At the moment all there are are
rumor De momento todo lo que hay son
conjectures spread by those
conjeturas extendidas por esas cuentas
Twitter accounts, even a little by
de Twitter incluso también un poco por
mine. What's
la mía yo me
wrong with you, she's
qué te pasa está
drunk, you know what it could be that
borracha sabes lo que podría ser que
she had a vibrator in her vagina,
tuviese un vibrador en la vagina mir
look Look, imagining that she has a vibrator
Mirad imaginando que tenga un vibrador
in her vagina in her
en la vagina en el
ass, chat, I'm cross-eyed, eh, I think It's that I get
culo chat estoy bizca eh creo Es que me
distracted playing with the
desconcentro jugando con el
vibrator, chat, okay, grow, I play with a
vibrador chat valeo crecer juego con un
shiner in my
brillador en el
[ __ ] while I play LoL, I have to
[__] mientras juego al LoL lo tengo
admit it. Hi sh, I'm F, friend of
que reconocer Hola sh soy F amiga de
Javi El pelucas. Who is Javi pelucas?
Javi El pelucas Quién es Javi pelucas Me
Can you confirm 100% that you
puedes confirmar al 100% que tú tampoco
are not the girlfriend of chocas either, thanks? I
eres la novia del chocas gracias No te
cannot confirm it to you, but you
lo puedo confirmar pero tampoco te lo
cannot lie to yourself either, the truth 100% nothing in
puedes mentir la verdad al 100% nada en
this life, don't say never is never Not even
esta vida no digas nunca es nunca Ni
this one, you know,
este sabes
but I don't know who
pero no sé quién es el
peluca is, I don't know who pelucas is, my face,
peluca no sé quién es el pelucas me cara
my face t  it sounds familiar but I don't know where I've
me cara t suena pero no sé dónde te he
seen you your face sounds familiar but I don't know where I've
visto me suena tu cara pero no sé dónde
seen you on instagram on twitter you
te he visto en instagram en Twitter you
know in many places the one who started
know en muchos places el que comenzó
all this was the chocas everything that is
todo esto fue el chocas todo lo que se
said against me is true and that he
diga mi contra es cierto y eso que él
had several suitors
tenía varias digamos pretendientas
willing to force the role with him and for
dispuestas a forzar el rol con él y por
whatever reason he noticed seling which I
lo que sea él se fijó en seling que yo
think he is attracted to something and started with
creo que algo le atrae y comenzó con
these pullit on his social networks
estas pullit en sus redes sociales
watching Carola is that watching Carola
viendo a Carola es que viendo a Carola
don't [ __ ] with me
no me jodas
man seeing celi
tío viendo a celi
that occupies the entire screen her enormous
que ocupa toda la pantalla su enorme
ass don't [ __ ] with me man you must have a
culo no me jodas tío lo tenéis que pasar
pretty bad time I guess right look that he had
bastante mal I Guess right mira que tuvo
gonzaba who tried to force the role and
a gonzaba que intentó forzar el rol y
be his biggest fan or the very
ser su mayor fan o a la mismísima
princess who already signed on some
princesita que ya firmó en alguna
occasion that she liked shas Although
ocasión que le gustaba el shas Aunque
now that I remember She stopped being the Crash
ahora que recuerdo Dejó de ser el Crash
of princess after her controversy with
de princesita después de su polémica con
the Ministry of Equality if you really
el Ministerio de igualdad si de verdad
collide I'm not totally serious
chocas no te lo digo totalmente en serio
if you really think that this
si tú de verdad te piensas que este
video is to hate someone This video is
vídeo es para odiar a alguien Este vídeo
focused on hating someone and not to give
va enfocado a odiar a alguien y no a dar
a message  that there are certain
un mensaje de que hay ciertas
situations that we have normalized that
situaciones que tenemos normalizadas que
shouldn't be normalized if you
no deberían de estar normalizadas si tú
think that this video that maybe you
te piensas que este vídeo que quizá te
think about it because it is focused in a certain
lo pienses porque va enfocado en cierta
part towards you And maybe you
parte hacia ti Y quizá te lo hayas
took it wrong and I totally understand but for
tomado mal y lo entiendo totalmente pero
you to think that this message is a
que tú te pienses que este mensaje es un
hate message is very very
mensaje de odio está es muy muy
wrong but very very wrong eh
equivocado pero muy muy equivocado eh
but this message is not a
pero este mensaje no es un mensaje de
hate message at all look at how things are that
odio para nada fijaros cómo está la cosa
even her own chat vaites it With
que hasta su propio chat lo vaitea Con
Celin what is Celin doing
celin qué hace celin
Who were you trying to snipe eh cow did you
A quién pretendías snipear eh vaca a
want to
querías
snipe and she obviously as you are
snipear y ella evidentemente como estáis
seeing in the clips is creating
viendo en los clip pues me está creando
confusion for me because I think she is
confusión porque es que creo que le
playing along with it and I think that here there is something
sigue el juego y creo que aquí hay algo
more snowy but having red hair in I
más nevado pero teniendo el pelo rojo en
love it I love it I love the ch I
me encanta me encanta me encanta el ch
have discovered it I love it finally
lo hab descubierto me encanta por fin
this woman tells the truth man
esta mujer dice la verdad hombre se
takes off the passive of woman and tells a
quita la pasiva de mujer y dice una
truth that nothing happens totally
verdad que no pasa nada totalmente
normal I also like it I like you
normal A mí también me
crash I
gusta me gusta chocas quiero
mean really you crash your partner
decir es en serio que chocas tu pareja
like this we have been together for years Yes Selin
así llevamos cu años juntos Eso sí selin
has signed on some occasion that for the
ha firmado en alguna ocasión que por el
moment  Well she's not interested in
momento pues no está interesada en los
men because it would disconnect her or
hombres porque la desconectara o la
distract her from her work and it would be a
desconcentrar en su trabajo y sería una
distraction along the way. Love
distracción en el camino el amor y tener
and having a partner right now in my life are only bad things, they distract me, they take my mind off goals and make me invest time, but I wanted her so much, minutes with her meant 10 hours with any other, love and having a partner right now in my life, well,
pareja ahora mismo en mi vida
another fallen soldier, boys, just
en fin otro soldado caído chicos al
like Shokas, have had girls
igual que el shokas ha tenido chicas
trying to force the role with him, she's
intentando forzar el rol con él ella
also had her SIM and no, I'm not
también ha tenido a su SIM y no no me
talking about this game where you
refiero al juego este en el que tú te
create your own house and manage your
creas tu propia casa y manejas tus
little dolls without pardos. For example, I
muñequitos sin pardos Por ejemplo yo
think Skin has been one of them, Sky
creo que skin ha sido uno de ellos Sky
tends to be quite a SIM of this type of
suele ser bastante SIM de este tipo de
women. It was with Abi, who fred him
mujeres lo fue con Abi quien lo fre sonó
very quickly and for whom he was dying for her
rapidísimo y por la que se moría por sus
bones. But I don't understand why you don't
huesos Pero no entiendo por qué no me
see me well, please try to argue it,
ves bien por favor int argumentarlo
you know what happens, I
sabes lo que pasa que vengo de
literally came from betting with you 100 200
literalmente de aposte contigo 100 200
How many subs were 100 and winning them in
Cuántos subs fueron 100 y ganarlos en
three days, that was  in January it was in January it's
tres días eso fue en enero fue en enero
been half a year now eh we're in
ha pasado medio año ya eh estamos en
July already but there would have been
julio ya pero también hubier hubo
precedents But what does it have to do with
antecedentes Pero en qué tiene que ver
cl t I have that perspective so I kind of
cl t yo tengo esa perspectiva entonces
maintain it and drag it a
como que la mantengo y la arrastro un
bit no And that lately I've noticed you
poco no Y que últimamente te he notado
a bit rude go to bed what have you said I haven't said
un poco borde acostarme qué has dicho no
go to bed have you
he dicho acostarme has dich qué has
said what have you said I told myself arrest what have you said I said that no I haven't
dicho me he dicho arrestar qué has dicho
said that I said drag No what have you said that I did that
arrastrar No qué has dicho
bet Ay ay ay to
que heicho eso apostar Ay ay ay a
bet I come from sleeping with you I come from a
apostar vengo de acostarme contigo vengo
bet I've scratched eh alone I said bet I said I said bet bet
aposte he dicho he dicho aposte apost
with you 100 subs weren't that I didn't
arme contigo 100 subs no eran que no
get back with my ex because we say no 143 I'm
volvida con mi ex por decimos no 143 yo
not going to give details but that was the no
no voy a dar detalles pero esa fue la no
nap time has proven me right like yes
siesta el tiempo me ha dado la razón en
every time so of course
plan que sí todas las veces entonces
Now what do I know in fact
claro Ahora yo que sé de hecho
recently in the Dallas debate with
recientemente en el debate de Dallas con
Ricky and Edie we found out that Kin
Ricky y edie nos enteramos de que kin
had something with Ricky Eddy's current girlfriend
tuvo algo con la actual novia de Ricky
whom
Eddy a la que habría conquistado de
would have conquered in ways as subtle as this Hey you know there is the same distance from here to here as from here but well It seems that with Selin it didn't work out for her Hey there is little talk about the po that [Music] Teo something very strange not like I blew you up it
Teo algo muy raro no en plan te reventé
was a do I don't
fue un do no
know sk could be a focus of ets of
segú sk podría ser un foco de ets de
streamers and casner And the thing is that removing
streamers y casner Y es que quitando
practically almost nobody likes that
prácticamente a casi nadie le cae bien
[Music]
[Música]
youtuber yes I
youtuber si
forget the problems my boyfriend crashes on the
olv los problemas mi novio se choca los
weekends and during the week sk to vary a
fin de semana y de sem sk para variar un
little I get bored of every day you crash
poquito me aburro de todo día chocas
all the time you
todo rato
crash Ah okay it's good to
chocas Ah está bien está bien para
balance out sol when she has argl
equilibrar sol cuando tiene argl
interested
interesa
maybe she's a streamer friend of delor segur
quisas es una streamer amiga delor segur
because she recently became Vidal and the thing is that they
porque hace poco se hizo Vidal y es que
banned her from Twitch because she
la banearon de Twitch porque se [__]
literally [ __ ] herself live she cleaned herself and
literalmente en directo se limpió y
showed the paper No no yes yes I [ __ ] myself yes
enseñó el papel No no sí sí me cago sí
a click that will haunt her for the rest of
un click que la perseguirá durante toda
her life everyone who follows her says
su vida todo el mundo que la sigue dice
that it's too obvious that Mara
que es demasiado obvio que a Mara le
likes Selin What Pon 3D and 2D yo  it takes me a
gusta selin Qué Pon 3D y 2D yo tardo
long time to fight okay I mean do
mucho en Luche vale o sea nos luchamos
we fight first or together to save
primero nosotros o juntos para ahorrar
water seriously it doesn't matter to you having
el agua serio no te da nada haberte
bathed next to Mara knowing her it must have happened to
bañado junto a Mara conociéndola seguro
me while I was looking at your
que se ha me dado mientras te miraba la
face the very Pig in fact not even
cara la muy Cerda de hecho ni siquiera
Mara herself has been able to deny that there
la propia Mara ha podido negar que
is some kind of thing between
exista algún tipo de rollete entre el
shokas and her friend selin al chocas I already
shokas y su amiga selin al chocas ya le
invited him to Japan and he rejected me It's the
invité a Japón y me rechazó Es la
first time a man rejects me
primera vez que me rechaza algo un
and it's not a joke eh leg you would beat
hombre y no es broma eh leg ganarias a
the girl I loved so much in falling in love with
la chica de la quería tanto en enamorar
choit papi I can make
al choit papi yo puedo enamorar al
chocas fall in love with you in a flash I don't
chocas de una pas que no lo
do it ul I only know you in specific moments
hago la ul se ti solo en momentos
a doubt really really and
concetos una duda de verdad de verdad y
also the streamer funkis who is a streamer
también el streamer funkis que es un
apparently quite close
streamer al parecer bastante cercano
to this circle has
también a este círculo ha firmado
categorically signed in a clip that
categóricamente en un clip que todo el
everyone knows that shas and selin have a
mundo sabe que shas y selin tienen un
thing that nothing happens totally normal
rollo que no pasa nada totalmente normal
to me too hey but at what
a m también me gusta Oye pero a qué
level is it a meme and aé level is it for real
nivel es meme y aé nivel es de verdad
I knew if I already knew that they come out that what and
sabía si ya lo sabía que salen que que y
chocas fan new months ago nov  where do you
chocas fan noved hace meses nov dnde
think he's going to
crees que se va a
move to the other guy's house [ __ ] and [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ] yes [ __ ] yes
mudar a casa del otro [__] [__] y
What
[__] [__] [__] sí [__] que sí What
7 months ago But how does he know So it's
hace 7 meses Pero cómo lo sabe O sea que
true but that was 7 months ago I'm
es cierto pero eso es hace 7 meses le
going to ask CP then [ __ ] true
voy a preguntar a CP entonces fuck true
or what do I know if you went he says that he hooked up 7 months ago
o yo que sé si fuis dice que se ha liado
how are they going to have hooked up
hace 7 meses cómo se van a haber liado
7 months ago what the [ __ ] are you telling me
hace 7 meses a mí qué [__] me contáis
chat do you think Celin tells me
chat os creéis que celin me cuenta con
all the people he has a l
todas las personas que tiene un l
or balls everyone you know that he
o [__] todo el mundo sabéis que le
's filming a series in which he's
está rodando una serie en la que está
inviting some creators to travel with
invitando algunos creadores a viajar con
him eh Juan was with him recently in
él eh yo Juan estuvo con él hace poco en
Japan but the first to participate in
Japón pero el primero en participar en
this series traveling to China was
esta serie viajando a China fue el
Chos himself then they ended up
mismísimo chocas luego terminaron
visiting Fran Cuesta at the sanctuary
visitando a Fran cuesta en el santuario
Well there's a clip with which
Pues bien hay un clip con el que se
this ship intensified a lot And it is that
intensificó muchísimo este ship Y es que
in a conversation Shokas talking about
en una conversación el shokas hablando
Selin could let it be known or at least that's what
de selin pudo dejar notar o por lo menos
Plex himself appreciated that
eso es lo que apreció el propio plex que
when he mentioned her his eyes lit up do you
cuando la mencionó le brillaron los ojos
want to have children Yeah by  supposed
quieres tener hijos Sí por supuesto
man when he finds the
hombre cuando encuentra la persona
right person Yes with zenin celin first he
indicada Sí con cenin celin primero
would have to lose weight because with
tendría que bajar los kilos porque con
that ass I don't fit in my house who is
ese culo No cabe en mi casa quién esen
a girl who is in love with me and
una chica que está enamorada de mí y a
you don't like her to me without more or it's that my
ti no te gusta a m sin más u es que mis
standards are very high already I mean what
estándares son muy altos ya O sea qué
standards do you have right
estándares tienes ahora
now to start with several
mismo para empezar varios
languages ​​a person with a
idiomas una persona con una cultura
very high general culture very intelligent chat
general muy alta muy inteligente chat
sient that is nice But you are you
sient que sea simpática Pero tú ereso tú
are blind nice honest and that is
eres ciego agradable honesta y que esté
good of course cin meets very few of
buena claro cin cumple muy pocas de de
those I'm going to tell you something your
esas te voy a contar una cosa te han
eyes lit up when you talked about
brillado los ojos cuando has hablado de
zenin Yes you think We played once and
zenin Sí tú crees Hemos jugado una vez y
what a disaster the fact that these two
qué desastre el hecho de que estos dos
commented on that while traveling made
comentaran eso estando de viaje hizo que
the ship go viral much more and
el ship se viralize mucho más y no
clips like this one kept appearing
parasen de aparecer clips en tiktok como
faithful to celin no no that she is faithful to me
este fiel a celin no no que me sea fiel
is what it has to do with
ella a mí es lo que tiene que
Tim lately he's been wanking a
que Tim últimamente anda pajareando
lot on Instagram Stories
mucho en las Stories de Instagram
what wanking on
qué pajareando en las Stories de
Instagram Stories but if the only thing I upload
Instagram pero si lo único que subo
stories is assembling furniture Crazy what
historia es montando muebles Loco qué
wanking man has no respect he's
pajareando hombre no tiene respeto
already trying to flirt  she must have
ya está intentando ligar tiene que tener
the messages from and I'm trying to
los mensajes los de y estoy intentando
flirt but if I spent the weekend
ligar pero si me pasé el fin de pasado
riding you move the whole [ __ ] weekend
montando mueves todo el [__] fin de
the private messages are packed and you
los privados a reventar y tú le
answer some story I don't answer
contestas alguna historia yo no contesto
anyone's stories a girl a girl
historias a nadie una tía una tía se
could be dying for me Bone and be
puede estar muriendo por mi Hueso y ser
a [ __ ] 10 a message from me is not going to reach her
un [__] 10 no le va a llegar un mensaje
no no it's not going to happen I mean how do you
mío no no va a pasar o sea tú cómo
proceed if you want to flirt with a girl
procedes si quieres ligar con una chica
she doesn't flirt with me you never I don't flirt
no liga ella conmigo tú nunca yo no ligo
You never they flirt with me I don't flirt You
Tú nunca ligan conmigo yo no ligo Tú
never No I'm iron I ignored her
nunca No yo soy hierro la ignoraba
so much that by the way I already know who
tanto que por cierto ya ya sé quién era
Celin was I mean I knew who it was what happens is I did
celin o sea sabía quién era lo que pasa
n't remember the name of course if we
que no me acordaba del nombre claro si
don't talk at the [ __ ] evening
no hablamos en la [__] velada
blex Well I think you two make a good
blex Pues yo creo que hacéis buena
couple
pareja
honestly Thank you very much let's see I'm the
sinceramente Muchas gracias a ver soy el
grandfather not of gossip like I'm
abuelo no del salseo en plan le saco
a few years older than some of these no
unos cuantos años a algunos de estos no
Although the chocas is on the way already eh
Aunque el chocas viene en camino ya eh
but I know a little about women as
pero conozco un poco a las mujeres al
well as the boys and what you're going to
igual que a los chavales y esto que Vais
see next is a
a ver a continuación es un ataque de
jealousy attack but by the book I mean  from the book
celos pero de manual o sea de libro
celin jealous let's see always seeing celin
celin celosa a ver siempre ver a celin
jealous is fun he got nervous with
celosa es divertido se puso nervioso con
a girl and said expressly that maybe
una chica y dijo expresamente que igual
you wouldn't like it very much the truth is that
a ti no te molaría mucho la verdad que
you make a good couple I don't know what you're waiting for
haceis buena pareja no sé a qué esperáis
look at it you bump into that blonde
mira que se vea chocas con la rubia esa
sucking the Chupa ch okay look how I
chupando el Chupa ch vale mira cóm lo
knew look how I knew stalker And
sabía mira como lo sabía acosadora Y
controlling is what she is and toxic look
controladora es lo que es y tóxica mira
how I already knew And I had already seen the
como ya lo sabía Y ya había visto el
video surely she signed her through
vídeo seguro que la fichó por
tiktok stalker and controlling is what she is
tiktok acosadora y controladora es lo
go with her when you see
que es te vaya con ella cuando vea nota
that she is selfish and has stolen all the
que es una interesada y le ha chado todo
[ __ ] money and only wants him for his fame
[__] dinero y solo le quiere por su fama
and his money then she realizes
y por su dinero entonces se da cuenta de
not to stick her nut in holes just to
no meter el churro en agujeros solo por
be like that okay Then you cry that oh It
estar así okay Luego lloráis de que ay
's that women are selfish that they are
Es que las mujeres son interesadas que
not men you have a girl sucking on the
no s hombre tees una tía chupando
microphone obviously wanting attention
micrófono queriendo obviamente atención
interest just because you're famous of course and
interés solo porque eres famoso claro y
not because I'm handsome celin I'm my [ __ ]
no porque soy guapo celin estoy mi [__]
Prime we surprise of Oh they cheated on me
Prime sorprendemos de Ay me pusieron los
chachan I have seen by the way I have seen
chachan he visto por cierto he visto a
celin over there I was over there you  I came to say
celin por ahí estaba por ahí te vin a
hello and yes she came because she
saludar y sí te vino ella porque también
's also a fan of course It's normal but oh well
es fan claro Es lo normal pero bueno no
it's okay she'll handle it well I don't know if she's going to be
pasa nada lo llevará bien no sé si va a
able to live well with the tension that there's going to
poder vivir bien con la tensión que va a
be I should do a Duo we should do
haber deberí hacer un Dúo tendríamos que
one but I got involved with a
hacer uno pero yo me he metido con un
Pro because I want to win son I'm
Pro porque Quiero ganar hijoa soy
too tryhard you're very tryhard Body
demasiado tryhard eres muy tryhard Body
absolute absolute kills me By the way Hey I
absoluto absoluto me mata Por cierto Eh
got the Chocas one but Look
me ha tocado la de chocas pero Mirad
who's behind Chocas's girlfriend
quién está detrás la novia del chocas
look at them there's two sides of the
mirarlos ahí está la doble cara de
coin Yes yes conclusions Let's see it's
moneda Sí sí conclusiones A ver es muy
still very risky to draw a conclusion
arriesgado todavía sacar una conclusión
from this but I predict that a relationship will come out of here I think that
de esto pero yo bticino que de aquí va a
very
salir una relación Yo creo que muy
soon I'm not going to be wrong and I think that
pronto no me voy a equivocar y creo que
very soon or maybe not so soon
muy pronto o a lo mejor no tan pronto
but not so far away we're not going to
pero sí no tan lejos tampoco vamos a
have the announcement that these two
tener el anuncio de que estos dos
confirm their relationship yes it's true
confirman su relación sí que es verdad
that there is a small mishap out there And the
que existe por ahí un pequeño percance Y
thing is that she just bought her
es que ella se acaba de comprar su
house in Seville and he in Madrid you
vivienda en Sevilla y él en Madrid ya
know that too And neither of them wants to
sabéis que también Y ninguno se quiere
move from where they live that could be a
mover de donde vive que eso puede ser un
big obstacle But well I also
gran obstáculo Pero bueno también te
tell you, I mean they are streamers who are
digo o sea son streamers a los que les
going  well I think they can go Hey,
va bien Creo que se pueden ir Oye pues
about 10 here, another day there and it
unos 10 para acá otros día para allá y
's basically working eh You don't have to
está rulando básicamente eh No tienes
fix your residence in one place
por qué fijar tu residencia en un sitio
but you can have two residences
sino que puedes tener dos residencias
So the thing is that I think that they do
Entonces es que yo creo que sí que se
like each other the truth I mean I know it's just a
gustan la verdad O sea sé que es
joke I know they're joking but
cachondeo sé que están con la broma pero
really I do think that there is a
realmente sí que creo que hay un
real flirtation eh one thing is a
coqueteo real eh una cosa es un
joke and another thing is a little joke
cachondeo y una cosa es una bromilla en
once in a while or any nonsense
de vez en cuando o cualquier tontería
but the fact is that
pero es que esto mismo lo están
they are feeding this with a certain tone that
alimentando ellos con cierto tono que a
makes me think as
mí me da que pensar como bien vio
ple himself also saw when he saw
también el propio ple cuando vio que se
Shokas's eyes light up talking
le iluminaba la mirada a shokas hablando
about Selin your eyes lit up when
de selin te han brillado los ojos cuando
you talked about Zenin I think that there are
has hablado de zenin creo que ahí hay
feelings there in the casap parneo issue
sentimientos en el tema casap parneo
Well although it may be probable that maybe
Pues si bien puede ser probable que a lo
Selin noticed him or caught her
mejor selin se fijas en él o le llamara
attention and started talking to him
la atención empezase a hablarse con él
because he's the chocas not that he has a lot of
porque es el chocas no que tiene muchos
numbers and such really casap parne Well I do
números y tal realmente casap parne Pues
n't know if he is casap parne much because
no sé si está casap parne mucho porque
his audience continues to be more or
su audiencia se sigue manteniendo más o
less less with what I already had between
menos menos con lo que ya tenía entre
2000 and 2500 viewers And the thing is that the
2000 y 2500 viewers Y es que la
LOL community is a little different from
comunidad de LOL es un poco diferente a
others Even if they do collaborations, they
otras Por más que hagan colaboraciones s
can make themselves more known and so on
que se pueden dar a conocer más y demás
But in the end The Followers are not usually
Pero al final Los Seguidores no suelen
shared with other streamers if
ser compartidos con otros streamers si
you follow a LoL creator you only
tú sigues a un creador del LoL solamente
see him or at least it is more common that it is like that
lo ves a él o por lo menos más habitual
and not like what happens in other
que sea así y no como pasa en otras
communities Like for example in the elite
comunidades Como por ejemplo en la élite
in the gossip, we share many
en el salseo no que compartimos muchas
audiences with many creators and it is What
audiencias con muchos creadores y es Qué
type of audiences like this like
tipo de audiencias como esta como la de
nissaxter's like el millor's, they are
nissaxter como la de el millor pues
usually from the creator and only See the
suelen ser del creador y solo Ven al
creator, they have profiles that I think
creador tienen perfiles que yo creo que
can be quite compatible and that they make a
pueden ser bastante compatibles y que
good couple And what do you think? I
hacen buena pareja Y ustedes qué pensáis
will be reading the comments box
os estaré leyendo la caja de comentarios
please with great respect okay And in the
por favor con mucho respeto vale Y en
next few hours you have another video, as I
las próximas horas tenéis otro vídeo lo
said, okay subscribe, share,
dicho vale suscribiros compartir dale
like and all those little things and a
like y todas esas cosillas y un beso
huge kiss, gorgeous
enorme guapísimos